外へ
ぎゃあー
君の近くへ…
外へ出なくては
この星の外へ
毎日のお決まりの道の外で
人の手の温かさを知ったように…
また一歩外へ
まだ知らぬ 何かを知るために
父の腕に抱かれ 連れられた部屋の外で
空の高さと世界の大きさを
知ったように…
聞いた事のない
自分自身の笑い声を知ったように…
母の体の外へ出て初めて
空気の冷たさと
目覚めのキッスはまどろむあなたに
あやかしリップなお姫様
出会いの切符は夢見るあなたに
まやかし VIP なエア・フォース
時間がないの いま何時？
授業開始の５分前
I have to escape.
急いでないの いま大事
あなたに出会う５分前
Like leaving your mother's body
and feeling the cold air
and the warmth of all the people.
ヴィーナスお隣さんなの
どうして？ 知らない間に
ジーザスお向かいさんなの
聞いてやばいの
大胆あいつの攻撃
バイバイ気づいてない振り
Like being outside, wrapped
in your father's arms,
大胆あいつの衝撃 まさに生き地獄
and discovering the limits of the
sky and the size of the world.
寝起きのキックは挨拶代わりに
生足いっつも傷だらけ
手持ちのチップをあの子に賭けたら
まばたきみっつでノック・ダウン
Like hearing yourself laugh for the
very first time at something
outside your comfort zone.
嫌いじゃないの 嫌なだけ
予測出来ないこの気持ち
Outside,
期待しないで 暇なだけ
あなたと消える５分間
to a distant planet,
ヴィーナスあの子はいつでもそうなの？
いまなら間に合う
to discover the limits of my knowledge.
ジーザス引き返せないの 早く気付いて
Taking another step outside,
and closer to you.
No!
嫌だ！
Nino?
ニノさん？
I wanna stay right here!
私はここにいたい
I'm tired of being kicked out or getting separated.
追い出されたり 離れ離れになるのは
もう嫌だ
Chapter 87: "Vow"
Tired?
もう？
うむ
よっよーし じゃあいよう！
Okay, then let's stay!
We'll be fine, I guarantee!
大丈夫 どうにかなるもんだぜ
どうにかってどうするの？
How? What're we gonna do?
Rec, why is this happening to us?
ねーリクさん
どうしてこんな事になったの？
There's always a reason behind everything, right?
物事には何にでも理由があるんでしょ？
Yeah, Rec!
そーだよリクさん！
The reason.
こうなった理由…
事を起こしたのは 俺の父さん
My father's behind all of this.
And the reason is probably...
そして その理由は多分…
me.
俺…
If I leave the area, they may abort
their development plans.
俺が河川敷から出て行けば
工事はないかもしれません
I knew from the start this could
happen. But for some reason...
本当は分かってたのに… なんでだろう
I couldn't bring myself to admit it.
口に出したくなかった…
But it's no big deal, right?
いいじゃないか 別に…
I'm from the outside world, anyway.
俺は元々
よそ者だし
I...
私は
I want to stay here
お前と みんなと
ここに一緒にいたいんだ！
with you and everyone else!
Please. I'm asking you as your lover.
恋人のお願いを叶えてくれ
H-Hey, Nino! If you need something,
you could just ask me!
ちょ… なあニノ お願いなら俺にしろよ！
I'm way more reliable than some tenderfoot
trying to turn tail and run.
“俺が出てけば～”なんて言ってる
へなちょこより全然頼りに…
I never should have let myself
become so pessimistic.
俺とした事が 弱気になっていましたよ
ふっ… 安心して下さい ニノさん
Don't worry, Nino. Your lover
is, as always, perfect!
あなたの恋人は パーフェクトです
Anything's possible.
為せば成る… 俺なら出来る 何事も！
I can do anything I put my mind to!
きゃあ！ リクかっこいい！
Rec, you're so cool!
Rec.
リク…
Time to execute my plan.
作戦開始です
I'll do whatever it takes to let Nino stay here!
絶対にニノさんをこの橋の下から
追い出させたりしません！
Ko Ichinomiya
M-M-M-Master Ko! It's been so long!
こここ… 行様～っ
お久しぶりにございますぅああっ
Rec brings his ultimate weapon online.
リクの最終兵器 起動です
Chapter 88: "Superior Aura"
Before you is the main office of
a major company called Goes.
ここは 一流企業“Goes”本社
A company headed by Rec himself.
リクが経営する会社である
My dear employees of Goes,
親愛なるGoes社員諸君…
I apologize for my extended absence.
ここ最近 留守がちですまなかった
But there's a very good reason for it.
しかしそれには訳があったのだ
I'm sure you've already looked over
the materials in front of you.
もう手元の資料は見てくれたと思う
As you view the project charter—
この企画書を見て…
いや 競合相手を見て
—no, as you realize who our competitor is—
Ichinomiya Corporation
Arakawa Development Project
—some of you may laugh at such an impossible
task! But I want you to believe in me.
無謀と笑う者もいるだろう
しかし 信じて欲しい！
This is something I've spent
a lot of time developing.
これは私が練りに練った…
この市ノ宮行が保証する
Arakawa Development Project
I, Ichinomiya Ko, promise you...
a victorious project!
“勝てる企画”であると！
ぬあっあっ… ぐっあっ…
Three days have passed since Rec left Arakawa.
橋の下から リクが出て行って三日
Just like Rec said. His dad's goons have
been coming and going every day now.
リクの言ってた通り 毎日のように
パパさんの会社の人が来てるなぁ…
They can't have any real work to do yet.
本当はまだやる事ねーだろうに…
You're right. They're just trying
to put pressure on us.
ええ 我々にプレッシャーを
かけているんでしょう
It disgusts me.
全く憎たらしい
You're looking good today, Sister.
What's with the grisly getup?
シスターは今日随分愛らしいなー
てゆうか完全に熊じゃね？
どしたの？
Oh, this. Rec told me I should wear a disguise
to avoid attracting attention from the police.
ああ これはリクに言われて…
警察呼ばれたら
絶対に捕まるから変装しろと
ちなみに 銃もカモフラージュですよ
As you can see, I've also disguised my weaponry.
えらいファンシーだなぁ
Very fancy.
I didn't want to add to Rec's stress while
he's out there busting his butt for us.
外で頑張ってくれてるリクに
余計な心配はかけられませんからね
True. He's the world's biggest worry-wart.
そーだなあ あいつは心配性だから…
あれ？ そこにいるのは
村長とシスター君？
Huh? Is that the Chief and Sister I see?
What happened to you?
どうしたの？ その格好
シロこそどうした 変装か？
You in disguise, too?
Rec said I should put this on
and just wander around.
いやぁ何かリク君に
これ着てうろついてって言われて
ふん やはり建設会社の奴らのせいか…
It must be to distract those company men.
I'd only need ten seconds
against a group that size.
本当ならあれ位の人数
10秒で済むんだが…
あっはははは… 何の秒数？シスター君
For what? Watch what you say, Sister.
Your ugly words clash with your cute looks.
今日折角可愛いんだから
言動に気をつけて
Besides, they're not so bad
once you get to know them.
それに 話せば分かってくれる奴らですよ
Yeah? I tried talking to one of them earlier,
but they weren't exactly friendly.
そうなのか？ さっき俺声かけたけど
あんま友好的じゃなかったなー
Actually, three seconds is plenty.
やはり ３秒でやります
Calm down, it's fine! Just wait here.
大丈夫だよ ちょっと待ってて
Rec taught me the magic phrase.
この前 リク君に魔法の言葉を
教わったからね
Magic phrase?
魔法の言葉…？
You mean, "I don't understand Japanese"?
ニホンゴ ワカリマセ～ン か？
Hey guys.
ねぇ君達？
あん？
Good work today. Feel free to head home now.
お疲れさん 今日はもうあがっていいよ
あ はい 主任
Thanks... Supervisor?
Thanks, Director!
部長 お疲れーっす
No, he's the manager!
バカ 課長だろ？
If you'll excuse us—
失礼しまーす
ふっはははは…
みんな素直ないい子達ですよ
They're all very well trained.
Hm. Maybe I should give it a shot next time.
ふむ 私も使ってみようかな…
You'd be perfect if we were at a theme park.
遊園地とかならいけるんじゃね？
Superior Aura
He takes advantage of his superior aura.
上司オーラ乱用です
Chapter 89: "Under the Bridge Without Rec"
いやー 話の分かる上司もいるんだなー
Man, I'm glad someone gets it.
Right? The deadline's nowhere in sight.
Why should we waste our time down here?
納期まだ先だし いたって別に
する事ねえもんなー
So... was he the manager, or the director?
でも あの人課長だっけ？ 部長だっけ？
いや…
No.
He was a total stranger.
やっぱりあいつ知らねー野郎だよ…
俺戻るわー…
I'm going back.
Who the hell was that?
何だあいつ！
ニコニコ上司面しやがって…
Acting like he was some big shot—
He was just mocking us!
バカにされたみたいで気分悪い！
If these people don't want us down here,
they should just tell us to our face.
大体追い出したいなら
回りくどい事しないで “出てけ”って…
Rec. Hey, Rec!
リク！ おいリク！
Welcome back.
おかえり
I've got three days worth of fish waiting for you.
３日分も魚が溜まってしまったぞ
You feeling okay? You haven't had
any fish for three whole days.
大丈夫か？
３日間魚食えなかっただろ？
Something about you looks different...
何だか人相が変わったなぁ…？
ひもじかったのか？
Are you malnourished?
ん？ あ！ リクこの野郎！
Huh? Rec, you bastard!
You said you wouldn't be back for a week!
お前１週間は帰って来れねぇって
言ってたじゃねーか！
お 俺はなぁ 悔しいけど…
I hate to admit it, but you might be the
only one who can help Nino this time.
今回ばかりは お前しかニノの願いを
叶えられねーだろうと…
I was writing a song to cheer you on.
応援歌なんて作ってたのに…
But I should have known you'd crap
the bed, you damn freeloader!
やっぱり買いかぶりだったぜ
このヒモ野郎っ！
Hey, Hoshi...
いや 星…
This might not be Rec.
何かこいつリクじゃ…
探したでリク…
I've been looking for you, Rec.
ステラ…
Stella?
I heard you've been scrambling around,
trying to save this place.
今わりゃあ この橋の下のために
頑張っとるらしいのぅ…
I'm touched by your efforts.
わしゃ感動したわ…
It's not much, but I've got something for you.
そんでささやかながらおんどれに
プレゼントじゃ…
秘孔…
Secret pressure point...
Quick Rest!
一休み！
Once he wakes up from his suspended
animation, he'll be chock-full of energy!
次に仮死状態から目覚めた時には
元気一杯じゃー！
Suspended—Did you stop
his heart or something?
仮死？ 何？
心臓止めちゃったの？
But you know, I don't think this is even Rec.
てゆうか こいつリクじゃねぇんだよ
Oh, you're right. Then who is he?
ん？ ホントじゃ 誰じゃこいつ
リクのご飯…
Rec's food—
Well, this guy'll just be dead to
the world for like three hours.
まあ～ ３時間位
死んだように眠るだけじゃ…
He will wake up, right?
起きんだよな…
ちょっとの間ですからー
It's just for a little while.
Going away is bad!
離れ離れは困るぞ
I'll be back in no time. I just have to take
care of some things at the office.
すぐ戻りますから！
会社で色々準備があるんです
It's so we can stay together in the long run.
これからも一緒にいるために
ちょっとの我慢です
Have some fish ready for me
when I get back, okay?
帰ったらまた 魚食わして下さいね…
Come back, already.
早く帰って来い…
もう３日もお前に会えなくて… 私は…
I haven't seen you in three days.
At this point—
No.
いや…
Well...
I'll remember when I see him.
見りゃ 思い出すだろ…
She's forgotten his face.
顔を忘れました
Chapter 90: "Father and Son"
Arakawa Development Project
That was amazing, Master Ko! I knew you'd do it!
さすがです 大変お見事でしたぞ 行様！
I didn't believe it could be done at first, a plan to challenge the Ichinomiya Group.
天下の市ノ宮グループに
喧嘩を売るような企画
初めはこの高井もまさかと思いましたが
But the proposal was perfect—more than
enough to convince the other executives.
ここまでの内容に仕上げ
かつ幹部達を納得させるとは…
All that work I put in was well worth it!
わたくしも走り回った甲斐が
ありましたぞ！
はははは！ 当然だ！
俺を誰だと思ってるんだね
Of course! Who do you think I am?
Father wasn't expecting any competition,
so his plan is full of loopholes.
父さんのプランは競合相手が
いないと思って隙のある出来だ！
It's not gonna be cheap. But we are
a top-tier company, after all.
多少予算は張るが うちだって一流企業
As long as there are no flaws in my own plan,
当日まで俺の参戦がバレなければ
victory is ours!
我々が勝てる
Yes, of course.
もちろんですとも
I am shocked.
驚いたな…
Yes, I never imagined he would resist like th—
ええ… まさか
こんな抵抗をなさるとは驚き…
I guarantee on my life that this project will end in success!
息子のバカさ加減にだ
I am shocked at my son's utter idiocy.
Thanks, Takai.
I am now forced to completely shatter his ego.
この機会に鼻を完全に
へし折ってやらなければいかんな
Redevelop the plan. Immediately.
一応計画を練り直しておけ
Understood.
了解しました
By the way, Master Ko...
時に行様…
I know it's not my place to say anything, but...
わたくしがこんな事を申すのは
出過ぎた事と思いますが…
What, Takai? Just say it.
どうした高井？ 言ってみろ
Why didn't you negotiate with your father first?
どうして お父様とこの件について
直接お話しなさらないのですか？
話をして 分かってくれる人なら…
If he were a man who could be negotiated with,
He wouldn't have tried to bury his son's
home in concrete in the first place.
何も言わずに息子の居場所に
コンクリを流そうとしたりしないよ…
Master Ko... no.
行様… あ いえ
Perhaps... your father is just as afraid to face you
お父様も…
人と向き合うのが怖いのでは
as you are him.
くっ この男 何をバカな…！
That man... what a fool!
行様 まさに出過ぎた事とは
思いますが…
Master Ko... I know this is well
beyond crossing the line, but...
この高井めを… パパと呼んでも
よろしいんですぞ…
Maybe you could
go ahead and call me Daddy?
Huh? Daddy?
Oh! One more, please! One more time, Master Ko!
おぉう！ ワ ワンモア 今のを
ワンモアですぞ行様ぁ～！
だから報告からこの男を
抹消する事は出来ないのか…
Can't we eliminate this man
from our reports somehow?
Takai, what—
One more time!
ワンモアプリーズ
One more, please!
I'm afraid not.
無理ですわ
何をだ！？ どうした高井！
What is this?!
One more what, Takai?!
Even Daddy loses his temper sometimes.
パパだって苦手な人がいます
Chapter 91: "The Plan"
人はそれぞれ 心の中に
“帰る場所”を持っている
We all have a place in our
hearts we long to return to.
Where we were born.
Where we hold special memories.
生まれた土地
幸せな思い出の残り香のある所
And...
そして…
A place where our beloved resides.
好きな人のいる所…
Nino! I've returned!
ニノさん！ 今戻りました！
Rec!
リク！ ふっ
高井さん久しぶりー！
It's been a while, Takai!
えへ 元気だったー？
How've you been?
ああ 高井さん！
Mr. Takai!
Good to see you again.
ご無沙汰してますー
Yo, Takai. Thanks for helping me out last time.
よっ高井… この間は世話になったな！
You look well.
お元気そうで…
Guys! Me! I'm home!
おいお前ら！ 俺アイムホーム！
I don't care about the others.
But Nino, you've got the wrong guy!
他の連中はいいとしてもニノさん！
ちょっとそれやる相手 間違えてますよ！
Welcome back, Rec!
おかえりリク
ごっ！ 忘れてたっぽい上にそっち！
She forgets my face, and now this?
行様 でしたら わたくしが間接ハグを…
Master Ko.
I'd be happy to transfer Miss Nino's hug to y—
No. That won't be necessary, Takai.
あぁ 気を遣わないでいい 高井
So, that was...
まぁその… 頑張れ
You'll be fine.
Anyway, I'm glad to see
everything's just how I left it.
けど良かった… 何も変わってませんねー
まぁ 何か立ち入り禁止の
テープとか貼られたが…
Well, they did put up all this
"keep out" tape everywhere.
But it feels weird being on
this side of it, ya know?
まったく… 内側にいるのに
おかしな光景よね
So anyway, Rec... what's the deal?
Do we get to stay here or not?
けどよーリク 結局どーなったんだよ
本当に俺らここにいられんのか？
You didn't give up and come
crawling back, did you?
途中で音を上げて
帰って来たんじゃねーだろーな！
ふん！ そんな訳ないだろう！
Perish the thought!
俺の完璧な企画書で…
この橋の下の開発権利を俺が取ります！
With my perfect planning,
I'll be assuming control of this
area's development rights!
おぉ これが河川敷再開発の企画書？
Yup. And I'll be bidding for
construction rights, as well.
ええ！ これでここの工事の
コンペに参加します
Wow, it's really easy to follow.
I'd expect no less of you, Rec.
へぇ～見やすいねぇ さすがリク君だ
そう言えばシロさんは
元営業マンだっけ…
That's right. I forgot Whitey
used to be a businessman.
Knowing that makes me a little nervous
about showing him my plan.
そう思うと 企画書見られるの
少し緊張するな…
な… 何ですか…？
What is it?
いやさ リク君…
Well, Rec... a park is meant to be
a place for everyone, right?
公園てのは色んな人が使う場所でしょ？
そう考えると
In that case,
are you sure the sidewalks should be brown?
歩道は茶色のタイルではなく
白にするべきじゃないかなぁ…？
Don't you think they should be white instead?
バリアフリーの観点から見てもね
But that's just my perspective.
いや 俺ら“渡ラー”の事まで
考えていられませんよ！
We can't always be catering
to "walkers," you know.
Don't try to come off like you're
thinking of everyone.
もっともらしく都合いい事
言わないで下さい！
The hell? Why doesn't this place
have a stage for live shows?
つーか 何でライブ会場がねーんだよ！
Stop messing around. Even if there were a stage,
no stupid satellite would get to sing on it.
ふざけんなよ！ あったとしても
天体の歌う場所はねーからな！
Hey, listen. A park should have lots of fertile dirt.
そうよ やっぱり公園は
土がいっぱいなきゃ
With lots of manure-based nutrients!
肥料を豊富に含んだ土がね！
And then put in a huge irrigation ditch,
and a road big enough for a tractor, and—
それから大きな水路を引いて
マニアスプレッダーが
通れる道も作って…
うん それもやんないし…
Yeah... not happening.
Rec.
リクよ これではいかんぞ！
I do not approve!
そうだよ！
Yeah!
What now?
シスターたちまで何を…
Don't you see? This park—
見て分からんのか！
この公園… 水路から侵入されたら
ひとたまりもない！
The waterway has absolutely no
defense against an invasion!
It's wide open on top, too.
空路もがら空きだし…
サイコキネシスガードもないじゃない！
There's no psychokinesis guard anywhere!
You have to do better than
this, or they'll come for us!
ちゃんとしないと奴らが来ちゃうよ！
What are you guys trying to protect against?!
あんたら何を阻止しようとしてんだよ！
What's with all these demands?
もー何ですか みんな 注文ばっかり！
そうだぞ！
He's right!
ニノさん！
Nino!
Why does it matter?
いいじゃないか何だって
十分じゃないか この場所で！
Isn't this place enough by itself?
ニノさん…
Nino—
All of you,
みんなと… リクと… あと些細な…
and Rec,
and just a small
launch pad. That would be enough, I think.
ロケット発射台さえあれば…
それで十分じゃないか…
じゃあ人工衛星でもいい！
And a satellite would be nice!
Your demands are all insane!
あんたら無茶苦茶ワガママですよ！
Chapter 92: "The Power of Ichinomiya"
Come on, people. Now isn't the time for this!
全く みんな 何ワガママ
言ってるんですか！
I've already handed this plan over
to the construction company.
この企画書はもう
工事委託企業にも渡してあるんだから…
もう変更はありませんよ
We can't make any more changes.
So your company isn't doing the construction?
工事をやるのは
リク君の会社じゃないの？
ええ うちは土建はやっていないので
No, my company doesn't handle that kind of stuff.
Ah, excuse me.
おっと 失礼します
Yes, thank you for your help
as always, Mr. Shimamoto!
はい！ お世話になっております
島本さん！
工事委託先の社長ですな
The president of the construction company.
Ah.
He's always ready to try something new.
Yes, yes! That was—
なかなか冒険心のある社長さんで…
白紙に戻して欲しい…？
それは荒川の件ですか？
You called to cancel?
You mean, the Arakawa project?
な 何で！？ 一体どういう事ですか！？
Why? What do you mean?
どうもこうも 競合相手は
お父様の会社だっていうじゃないですか…
What do I mean? I just found out that your
father's company is competing for the contract.
あぁ！ それは初めから言って…
But I told you that bef—
わたしゃてっきり！
Well I thought...
I figured it was just a good-natured competition
with consent from both of you.
両社了解の上の出来レース的なものかと
思っていたのでね…
そんな…
But—
It's fine! We can still win the
contract regardless! So please—
大丈夫ですよ
正攻法でいっても勝てますよ！
だから一緒に…
Goesさん…
間違って勝ってしまったりしたら…
Mr. President...
Even if we did win by some fluke,
that'd be an even bigger problem!
それこそ“事”なんですよ
You have no idea just how
powerful Ichinomiya is.
Goesさんは市ノ宮の恐ろしさを
分かってらっしゃらない
All that awaits his competitors is...
市ノ宮に歯向かった者の末路…
Maybe you're not scared since
he's your father, but...
あなたにとっては父親ですから
怖くないでしょうが…
Please!
そんな！
実は我々は昨日 何名か荒川に
下見に向かわせたんです
We actually sent a few guys down there
yesterday to check out the area.
I could hardly bear listening to the report.
報告を聞いて震えましたよ
無数のブービートラップに道を阻まれ
They all got caught in bizarre booby traps
before they could even reach the water.
河川に入る事もかなわなかったと…
Ichinomiya is all that I've heard and more.
I have no choice but to withdraw!
市ノ宮は噂通りの男です…
この件はなかった事にさせて頂きます！
どうしたリク 顔色が悪いぞ？
What's wrong, Rec? You don't look well.
YOU PSYCHOPAAATH!!!
この野郎ーっ！
Chapter 93: "TEL"
The construction company canceled?
建設会社が断ってきたですと？
一体なぜ…
But... why?
Yeah, why?
なぜだ？
いや シスターのせいじゃない…
No, Sister's not to blame.
I know all too well what effect the
Ichinomiya name has on any company.
どの会社にとっても
市ノ宮の名前は脅威…
そんな事ぐらい
分かっている筈だったのに…！
もうっ こんな時に
村長はどこに行ったのよ！
Ugh! And where's the Chief when we need him?!
That's true. I haven't seen him since yesterday.
そういえば昨日から見ねーな
Rec...
リクさん…
What's gonna happen to us?
僕達どうなっちゃうの…？
I have no choice.
こうなったら…
"Maybe you're not scared since
he's your father, but..."
あなたにとっては父親ですから
怖くはないでしょうが…
Don't be stupid. I understand his
full power more than anyone.
バカ言うんじゃない… 父さんの怖さは
俺が一番良く知っている…
Is this your cellphone number, Father?
これ 父さんの携帯番号ですか？
That's right. Only a few close people have it.
そうだ ごく身内の者しか知らん
When's a good time to call you, usually?
いつなら電話してもいいですか？
Any time. When to call isn't an issue.
いつでも構わん 問題は時間ではなく…
The question is, do you have either right
or reason to take up my valuable time?
私の時間を奪うに値するだけの理由と
権利がお前にあるかどうかだ
Ichinomiya Seki
Outgoing Calls
Takai Terumasa
Search
Details
Submenu
どうした？ リク 何考えてるんだ？
You better not be thinking about leaving again.
まさかまた自分が出て行けばなんて…
ちっ 違いますよ！ 大した事じゃ！
No, that's not it!
It's nothing.
I'm just gonna call my dad real quick.
ちょっと父さんに電話するだけですから
Rec, are you really okay?
リク… お前… 本当に大丈夫か？
Yes, of course! I'm overflowing with energy!
ええ もう元気一杯ですが？
Those knees don't lie.
膝は正直ね…
うう… ごくっ んっ
This is... my last resort.
これが… 最後の手段
I'll just...
父さんに… 直接電話します…
call him directly.
He said before, his father is
あいつの親父さんは…
核より怖いらしいぞ
scarier than nuclear war.
ただ今の時刻は
-午後２時45分です
-ああ…
Who the hell did you just call?!
どこに電話してるんだテメェー！
Chapter 94: "Arakawa Qwik-Skit Challenge"
The illusionist! Princess Stella!
あの日夕暮れ
愛のカケラ 探すたびに
Tadaaa!
いつも何故か 寂しくなる
As you can see...
Not one damn scratch!
Thank you
Woohoo!
もう行かなくちゃ
この空泣き出す前に
What do you have today,
Shimazaki?
Takai has requested to have
his business cards reprinted.
サカサマになって
He's requested to
change his title to
君の事探して
"Just Above Secretary, Closer to Daddy Surrogate."
Next time, on 12 BRIDGE!
いつまでも僕らは
I told you, Shimazaki, I don't want
to hear any more about that man!
たどり着けないまま
Immortal
Masked Brothers
We'll protect the riverbank's peace!
Illustration: Ahn Dongshik
橋の下に立って
流れる渦に在って
いつまでも僕らは
その答え探して
イリュージョニスト！
プリンセス・ステラ！
はいぃー！
ご覧の通りー
まったくの無傷じゃい！
あはっ
やったー！ うふふふっ
やったー！…
ふん！
報告しろ 島崎
高井が名刺を刷り直したいと
申し出たそうです
新しい肩書は社長秘書以上
パパ未満にしたいと
次回 「12 BRODGE」
言ったはずだ島崎
奴の報告は一切要らないと